It's called War V, my especially killer, but we're getting more and more.
I'm not that correct.
I'm getting the case in about here.
Hopefully all this.
All right, unless these people here have thought of me,
I'll put them in on and so I get all that.
I'll put them in on and so I'll let them in.
I'll let them in.
Thank you for their willingness to support me.
Bless me.
And Father, we have to bring them to the zoo.
Lock it by our fighters.
For Shishmongers.
Please.
And to give them a special protection.
We've done them.
They've called them.
They want to prove it.
And we're just blessed by community.
Thank you.
Dear.
More of them.
They want to support us.
Bless this meeting tonight.
Help all these issues.
They should be.
The student wisdom.
You should name up for it.
Can you help me?
But the students do not have to say it to them.
And it's due to the Republic for racist stance.
One nation.
I don't even know.
Thank you.
The four.
They put racism here.
Personal cases.
Have it.
Five.
Two.
Three.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Two.
Eight.
Five.
Seven.
Six.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Four.
Five.
Eight.
We said 7,000 and 8,000, and 8,000, and we're going to start with the number of 100.
Those were primarily times when they were preparing for the briefing for 800 dollars, and they did a lot of shit to you.
You said 7,000 and 8,000 and 8,000, and you're going to start with 7,000.
So, that's it.
It is the code that the children will have to put in the strap.
I'm making motion here.
Sorry.
Are you making that motion?
Yes.
Step.